# JIN LEE

Canada • +1/2136165183 • leejin.dev@hotmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/jin-lee-791281199/ leejin.herokuapp.com/

## React/React Native Developer

## About me

Dedicated and efficient React/React native Developer with 6+ years of experience focusing on delivering exceptional products through a culture of teamwork, innovation, and development.

Certified in F/E technologies.

Specialized in React and React Native web applications.

Have ability to learn and use technologies, to work in team environment as well as independently to get things done, and to write efficient, clean, modular and maintainable code and take meeting everyday.

Seeking to further improve React and React Native skills as the further JavaScript Developer at Atmospheric Solutions, and looking for a good job as a team lead or React Developer.

## Skills

- JavaScript / ES6+, TypeScript
- React / Redux
- Redux Saga
- React Native
- NativeBase
- Realm / AsyncStorage

- ZURB foundation
- AWS
- Firebase
- Agile Software Development
- Test-driven Development (TDD)
- Git

## Employment

2017 - 2018

React/React Native Developer

### ELEKS Inc.

- Worked as a React Developer.
- Developed web applications using Meteor, React and React Native to facilitate client engagement.
- Developed several Hotel Booking app and Travel site apps.
- Managed and developed a data ingestion system for funding and company valuation data—including monitoring, reporting, and load-balancing systems.
- Offered development services for a cybersecurity company where they work on cloud-based systems

Technologies: React, React/Native, Redux, Redux Saga, ZURB foundation, NativeBase, Realm, AsyncStorage, Agile

## 2015 - 2016 Frontend Developer

Wappier Inc.: Intelligent Revenue Management

- Built the company's time tracking system in which 100+ employees would use on a bi-weekly basis using Google API.
- Collaborated with UI/UX designers, designers, and a team of Java back-end developers.
- Maintained and added new features to Yext's custom client platform that allowed company information to stay consistent on all social media platforms.
- Designed and developed user interfaces optimized for mobile platforms.
- Created wireframes and mockups of web applications based on department specifications. Developed prototypes, websites, and applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React, Redux, jQuery, SASS, Photoshop

### 2013 - 2015 Back End Developer

Sayenko Design Inc.

- For the first 1 year, I built custom WordPress websites that are responsive, clean, modern, and user focused. A web design project was broken up into four phases strategy, design, development, and training.
- For the next 1 year, I mainly worked for back end development with PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codelgnitor.
- For the last year, I worked on the field of Node. Js projects and developed 2 projects.

## Education

## 2017 - 2017 React native programming

Udemy.com Online Course

- Understand React Native with Hooks, Context, and React Navigation
- Use React Native and my React knowledge to build native iOS and Android Apps
- Master the advanced topics of React Native: Animations, Maps, Notifications, navigation and More

#### 2016 - 2017 International Business

Bachelor's degree - Harvard Business School Online

- Develop a data mindset and the analytical skills to interpret and communicate data.
- Master a proven framework for building and financing new ventures and make your entrepreneurial dreams a reality.
- Develop the leadership skills to advance your career, team, and organization.

### 2008 - 2012 Computer Science

Bachelor of Science - Centennial College

- Introduction to Mathematical Proofs
- Calculus
- Introduction to Computer Science
- Communication Skills for Computer Scientists
- Rhetoric and Media
- Effective Writing

## Recent Projects

#### 2019 - 2019 Hotel Booking - React Native

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cheaphotel.armanhotel

- Developed the search engine of finding cheap hotels around the world
- Get the best Hotel Deals & Offers

- Developed the engine discovering last minute hotels deals to save money
- Implemented the currency exchange from all around the world.
- Provided multiple filter options.
- Store the the guest reviews, ratings & experiences
- Developed Friendly & easy-to-use interface

Technologies: React, Redux, React Native, NativeBase, Realm, AsyncStorage, React Native Elements.

#### 2018 - 2019 Lift - MERN Development

## https://lift.co

- Created several pages such as Homepage, Products list and detail page, Brands list and detail page, accessories list and detail page, reviews page, etc
- Implemented API integration using Redux Saga
- Created RESTful APIs for getting data from MongoDB such as products, reviews, brands, etc.
- Implemented integration with various third party services such as Survey Gizmo, Active Campaign, GTM, Cron Jobs, Cohesion DB, Neilson DMP, etc.
- Developed Recommender engine and Effects search engine.

Technologies: React, Redux, Redux Saga, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Redis, Survey Gizmo, Active Campaign, Contentful, GTM, Cron Jobs, Cohesion DB, Nielsen DMP, Adbutler, etc.

#### Kiddom.co - MERN Development 2017 - 2017

## https://www.kiddom.co

- Created several pages such as Homepage, Classes page, Curriculum page, dictionary page, My Content page, etc.
- Implemented Reports page for showing the activities via Chart.
- Implemented delivering top-rated digital curriculum to students.
- Developed search engine by Subject and resource type

Technologies: React, Redux, Redux saga, React Material UI, Node.js, Express.js, Redis, MongoDB, D3.js, Chatbot, ...

#### 2016 - 2016 Brooks - Vue/Laravel

## https://www.brooksrunning.com

- Created efficient components and pixel-perfect pages
- Implemented integration with various 3rd party services such as Payment method, GMap, Google Tag Manager, Mux Video, and so on
- Created RESTful APIs using Laravel Framework.
- Developed the Shoe finder and Store finder functionalities.
- Developed the shoe search engine.

Technologies: Vue, Vuex, Laravel, Google Map, Google Tag Manager, Mux Video, Payment method

#### ZINGZING.TV - Angular/AWS 2015 - 2015

### https://www.zingzing.co.uk/

- Worked as a FE Developer
- Implemented Real-time database using AWS services.
- Developed the TV programme search engine
- Implemented setting a Reminder on certain TV programme.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Angular, Zone.js, AWS